迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我希望我们首先考虑的是
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So the first thing
I want us to think about is
定义字典。
defining a dictionary.
有人能帮我把这个充实一下吗？
So can someone help me flesh this out?
我知道这不是字典。
I know this is not a dictionary.
帮助我创建一个使用类型参数的字典。
Help me create a dictionary
that uses a type parameter.
所以我可以用数字、字符串或字符串数组来创建一个字典。
So I can make a dictionary with numbers,
or strings, or string arrays.
我需要在这里改变什么？
What would I need to change here?
Mike North: 我们刚刚讨论了泛型和类型参数。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So we've just been talking
about generics and type parameters.
我这里可能需要点东西。
I probably need something up here.
是什么使字典成为字典？
What makes a dictionary a dictionary?
它和数组有什么不同？
How's it different from an array?
演讲者2: 所有的值都是相同的类型。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: All of
the values are the same type.
Mike North: 所有的值都是相同的类型。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: All of the values
are of the same type.
所以我们会有一些东西，然后是 t。
So we're going to have something,
and then T.
这些价值观是如何在字典中组织起来的？
And how are the values organized
within the dictionary?
音箱3: 键值对。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Key value pairs.
Mike North: 键值对，以及我们如何键入任意值
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Key value pairs,
and how do we type an arbitrary
在打字稿中的键访问，我可以在这里传入
key access in TypeScript
where I can pass in
家里、办公室或者 iPhone，然后拿回一个电话号码？
home or Office or iPhone and
get a phone number back?
演讲者2: 你有一个数组，其中有 k 冒号，然后是类型。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So you have that array
where k colon and then the type.
迈克 · 诺斯: 完美的描述。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Perfectly described.
演讲者2: k 在某种程度上有什么特别之处吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is the k special in any way,
or can that be anything?
迈克 · 诺斯: 可以是我们想要的任何东西。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It can be whatever we want.
演讲者2: 那是惯例吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is that convention?
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我把它叫做 k，因为它是一把钥匙。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
I call it k, because of key.
这相当于命名一个函数参数，并且
It's the equivalent of naming
a function argument, and
就是这种类型的。
this is just the type that goes with it.
好了。
There we go.
我会按照惯例
And I'm gonna follow
the convention of acknowledging
如果我输入密钥我可能什么也得不到。
that if I pass in key I
might get nothing back.
如何将它添加到这个类型中？
How would I add that to this type?
演讲者2: 或未定义的问号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Or undefined question mark.
迈克 · 诺斯: 很好，事实上，我们得到了两个很好的答案。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Good, actually,
we got two good answers.
所以我可以这样做
So I can do it this way and
我要出去了
I'm gonna go out
在这里的肢体，哎呀。
on a limb here, oops.
是的，看起来可选项不起作用。
Yep, looks like the optional
is not gonna work.
这是一个很好的猜测，我们,
That's a very good guess though, that we,
我希望这是他们将来会引进的东西。
I would expect that to be something
that they'd introduce in the future.
没有什么能阻止他们。
There's really no,
nothing is stopping them.
事实上，我不想在这里深入研究更高级的东西。
In fact, I don't wanna get too deep
into more advanced things here.
有一种方法可以用问号来指定，但是两者都是
There is a way that you could specify
with the question mark, but you're both
要么我们引入值未定义的可能性。
right in that either we'll introduce the
possibility of the value being undefined.
很好，那么根据这些东西的使用情况,
Great, so
according to the use of these things,
如果这些是独立的功能。
if these are gonna be like
free-standing functions.
我们要传递的第一样东西是一本字典。
The first thing we are gonna
pass in is a dictionary.
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我们要把它做成一个 DictT。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
we're gonna make it a DictT.
它说找不到名字 t。
It's saying cannot find name T.
有人知道这里少了什么吗？
Anyone have an idea of
what's missing here?
演讲者2: [听不见]麦克 · 诺斯: 约束？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Mike North: A constraint?
我认为我们现在不需要限制。
I don't think we need
a constraint right now.
讲者2: 功能 t 是 t。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Function T is T.
Mike North: Function 应该有一个通用的 t，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Function should
have a generic T, right?
我们必须事先声明。
We have to state kind of up front that.
这个函数和 t 一样不是对一个叫做 t 的接口的引用,
This function, like T is not
a reference to an interface called T,
这个函数有一个类型周长，叫做 t，很好。
there is a type perimeter that this
function uses and it is called T, great.
我要在这里加上映射函数。
And I'm gonna add
the mapping function here.
所以从概念上来说当我们使用 array.map 时,
So conceptually, when we use array.map,
你怎么描述我们传入的函数？
how would you describe
the function that we pass in?
它的目的是什么？
What's its purpose?
演讲者2: 循环遍历你所有的数组？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: To loop through
whatever array you have?
Mike North: 当然，我们迭代调用这个函数。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Sure,
we iteratively invoke that function.
这个函数是做什么的？
And what does the function do?
演讲者4: 转化它 迈克 · 诺斯: 它改变了它,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Transforming it.
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It transforms it,
可能从一种类型转变成另一种类型，对吗？
potentially from one type to another type,
right?
在这种情况下，我们可能需要一个 t 的论点,
So, in this case,
we should probably take an argument of T,
因为我们正在迭代具有 t 值的数据结构。
cuz we're iterating over data
structure that has values of T.
我们还吐出了别的东西。
And we're spitting out something else.
我想引入另一个类型参数，因为这就是我们要转换的内容。
I want to introduce another type parameter
because that's what we're transforming to.
我马上就会填充这个函数，但是
And I'll fill in the function in a second,
but
我们要返回这些变换后的值的字典。
we're gonna return a dictionary
of these transformed values.
现在剩下的就是定义函数本身了。
Now all that's left is for
us to define the function itself.
麦克 · 诺斯: Arg 是 t，它返回 s。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Arg is a T and
it returns an S.
演讲者2: 你能忽略索引的论点吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Can you
ignore the index argument?
麦克 · 诺斯: 我可以忽略索引的论点吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Can I
ignore the index argument?
说话人2: map 函数中的第二个参数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The second
argument in a map function.
迈克 · 诺斯: 你可以，它不会，就像使用 array.map,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: You could, it wouldn't,
like in terms of using array.map,
那会有点违背我们的初衷。
that would sort of defeat the purpose.
函数是要完成的工作的定义。
The function is the definition
of the work to be done.
我们可以让它是可选的，然后返回相同的字典,
We could make it optional and then
just return the same dictionary again,
但对我来说，这是滥用的标志，对吗？
but to me that would be a sign of misuse,
right?
我们所能做的就是遍历数组，什么也不做。
All we could do is iterate
over the array and do nothing.
没错，所以没有指示如何从一种类型转换到另一种类型,
Right, so without instructions as to how
to transform from one type to another,
我想说这没有意义。
I would say there's no point in this.
所以在这种情况下，我会保持强制性。
So I would keep it mandatory in this case.
说话人2: 我的意思是类似于函数类型 Arg 是 t，但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I mean like for
the function type Arg is T, but
这个函数的第二个参数是
then as the second argument
of that function Is
类型编号的索引迈克 · 诺斯: 对不起，谢谢,
an index of type number
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Sorry, thank you,
当然。
absolutely.
迈克 · 诺斯: 是的，我们完全可以这么做
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yeah we
could totally do that and
我们不需要让它成为可选的。
we don't need to make it optional.
因为类型等价的工作方式,
Because the way that
the type equivalent works,
如果一个函数选择不接受这个参数，那没关系。
if a function chooses to not
receive that argument, that's fine.
如果我们让它成为可选的，我们是在暗示我们可能提供了它，但是
If we made it optional, we're indicating
that we may be providing it, but
它可能是未定义的,
it could come through as undefined,
这是不可能发生的，所以让我们执行这个。
which is not what's likely to happen,
so let's implement this.
很方便，创建一个空字典很容易，对吧？
Conveniently, it's easy to create
an empty dictionary, right?
我们要创造一个空字典。
We're gonna create an empty dictionary.
我们要循环遍历现有的字典
We're gonna loop over
the existing dictionary and
填充我们将要返回的东西。
populate the thing that
we're going to return.
然后我们会把它还回去。
And then we'll return it.
迈克 · 诺斯: 这就对了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So there you go.
这是简单的部分，现在我们如何迭代对象的键？
That's the easy part, and now how do
we iterate over an object's keys?
演讲者2: 反对。钥匙 Mike North: 好，反对。钥匙(dict) ,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Object.keys
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Good, Object.keys(dict),
我只需要使用 forEach
and I'll just use forEach, and
它接收一个值和一个索引。
this receives a value and an index.
这将有助于传递下去。
And that'll be useful to pass along.
我们会把它放在输出字典里,
And we'll say we're gonna place
in the output dictionary,
不好意思我要把这个改个名字,
sorry I'm gonna rename this for clarity,
在同一个字典键下，我们接下来做什么？
under the same dictionary
key what do we do next?
迈克 · 诺斯: 必须使用这个功能，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Gotta use that function,
right?
我差不多完成了，但还没用到。
I'm almost done and I haven't use it yet.
Mike North: 这个函数的作用是在索引中输入 t，然后返回 s。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So this function is made
to take in a T in an index and return S.
麦克 · 诺斯: dict 和，dKey。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: dict and, dKey.
太好了，谢谢。
Great, thank you.
迈克 · 诺斯: 这是 t 型的还是未定义的，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
this is of type T or undefined, right?
因为从理论上讲，这本词典里可能缺了点什么。
Cuz In theory, there could be
something missing in this dictionary.
可能是有人故意给我们设置了一个不确定的价值。
Could be someone who's deliberately placed
an undefined value in there trolling us.
迈克诺斯: 如果，迈克诺斯: 这个项目和
&gt;&gt; Mike North: If,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: This item and
将返回，对不起，不返回，我们将只
will return, sorry, not return, we'll only
如果定义了输出项，则将其放入此字典中。
place the output item in this
dictionary if it's defined.
我得小心点。
I've gotta be careful here.
我刚刚意识到零和空字符串还有其他麻痹的东西怎么办？
I just realized what about zeroes and
empty strings and other palsy things?
迈克 · 诺斯: 就是这样，这样更彻底，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: There we go,
that's more thorough, right?
所以我们循环遍历字典中的所有键。
So we're looping over all of
the keys in the dictionary.
如果有定义的话，我们就得到每个值。
We're grabbing each value if it's defined.
转换它，传递它，使用这个函数转换它
Transform it, pass it along that,
transform it using this function by
传递原始值和索引，得到转换后的值。
passing along the original value and the
index, we get the transformed value out.
现在我们把这个还回去。
And now we return this thing.
这是我们正在使用的地方，我们可以指向我们正在使用的地方
This is a place where we're using,
we can point to the places we're using
类型参数，这是很有必要的，对吗？
the type parameters, and
it's quite necessary, right?
所以我们收集了一本 t 型的字典。
So we take in a dictionary of type T.
T 可以帮助我们输入用于转换的函数。
T helps us type the function
we're using to transform.
我们接收到的函数会返回一些东西，这就是我们将要做的
And the function we receive returns
something and that how we'll be
能够弱化什么 s 应该和这决定了我们的输出类型。
able to infirm what S should and
that determines our output type.
看看我怎么用这个。
So check out how I can use this.
我已经创建了一个，没有。
mapDict, do I have one already created,
no.
所以我们要创建一个，我们只需要字符串。
So we'll create a, we'll just strings.
Mike North: 我在这里有一个函数，它把字符串当作
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And I'll have a function
here that'll take the string as
争论。
an argument.
Mike North: 如果我返回一个字符串数组,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And
if I return an array of strings,
mapdict 将返回字符串数组的字典。
mapDict will return
a dictionary of string arrays.
如果我把它包在这样的物体里,
If I where to wrap it
in an object like this,
这是我们已经见过的函数体的错误函数。
it's error functions we've
already met as a function body.
现在它是一个包装值的字典。
Now it's a dictionary of
sort of wrapped values.
注意，我必须使用类型参数来定义这个东西的作用,
Notice I had to use type parameters
to define what this thing does,
但是在我所说的地方，这看起来相对简单。
but where I'm calling it,
this looks relatively simple.
类型只是工作，空格填写，和
The types kind of just work,
the blanks are filled in, and
它们是由我传递给这个函数的参数推断出来的。
they're inferred by the arguments
that I'm passing to this function.
它们不需要被明确指定。
They don't have to be
explicitly specified.
这就像一口井
So this will be like a well
选择泛型的使用，因为它是一段非常灵活的代码。
chosen use of generics in that it's
a really flexible piece of code.
返回的类型。
The types that it returns.
你有足够的特异性和
You have as much level of specificity and
你需要的细节，以便继续进行。
detail that you need in
order to carry them forward.
我不需要提供任何明确的信息。
And I don't have to
provide anything explicit.
我们将确保减少行动的解决方案在回购协议中。
We'll make sure that the solution to the
reduce exercise here will be in the repo.
它遵循一个类似的模式。
And it follows a similar pattern.